<chunked_documents>
<chunk number="1">
<language1>
Page 1
melaksanakan Fungsi Penyelesaian (berkenaan transaksi Kad dan/atau E-Debit) setiap hari sebelum 2300 
jam, jika gagal berbuat demikian Bank berhak mengenakan kepada Pedagang fi penyelesaian lewat 
setara dengan 1.8% amaun transaksi yang dinyatakan pada Resit Terminal atau Diskaun Pedagang, 
mengikut mana yang lebih tinggi, tanpa menjejaskan hak Bank menurut Fasal 15, 16, 17 dan 18 di dalam 
ini.
</language1>
<language2>
Page 1
execute the Settlement Function (in respect of Card and/or E-Debit Transaction) every day before 2300 
hours, failing which the Bank is entitled to charge the Merchant a late settlement fee equivalent to 1.0% 
of the transaction amount indicated on the Terminal Receipt or the Merchant Discount, whichever is 
higher without prejudice to the rights of the Bank in Clauses 15, 16, 17 and 18 herein.
</language2>
</chunk>

<chunk number="2">
<language1>
Page 1
Soalan Lazim  
4. Setiap transaksi tanpa-sentuh merangkumi kod unik yang berubah dengan setiap pembelian, ia hanya 
boleh digunakan sekali sahaja dan hanya boleh dijana oleh cip di dalam Kad Debit tanpa-sentuh yang 
asal, dan ia mencegah Kad Debit palsu daripada dihasilkan menggunakan butiran keselamatan kad yang 
dicuri.
</language1>
<language2>
Page 2
Frequently Asked Questions 
4. Each contactless transaction includes a unique code that changes with each purchase, which can only 
be used once and can only be generated by the chip in the original contactless Debit Card, and prevents 
a counterfeit Debit Card from being produced from the intercepted card security details. In the unlikely 
event of fraud, you will not be held responsible for fraudulent charges or unauthorised purchases made 
using the contactless feature on your chip card. You must notify us immediately or as soon as reasonably 
possible of any unauthorised Debit Card use or any suspicious activities.
</language2>
</chunk>

<chunk number="3">
<language1>
Page 1
Pelanggan tidak dibenarkan untuk membuat pengeluaran wang di mesin ATM terpilih ketika sedang 
melancong di luar negara. 
Program ini termasuklah transaksi-transaksi JomPay dan transaksi berkaitan kerajaan; pembayaran bil 
FPX
</language1>
<language2>
Page 2
Customer is allowed to make cash withdrawal at selected ATM machines when travelling overseas. 
The Programme shall exclude all Government, JomPay, and/or FPX bill payment related transactions
</language2>
</chunk>
</chunked_documents>